Only those you trust can truly betray you.
The Wizard of Lies is a crime, drama, history film directed by Barry Levinson.
A look behind the scenes at Bernie Madoff's massive Ponzi scheme, how it was perpetrated on the public and
the trail of destruction it left in its wake, both for the victims and Madoff's family.
Bernie Madoff, played by Robert De Niro.
Ruth Madoff, played by Michelle Pfeiffer.
Frank Dipascali, played by Hank Azaria.
Stephanie Madoff, played by Kristen Connolly.
Catherine Hooper, played by Lily Rabe.
Mark Madoff, played by Alessandro Nivola.
The Wizard of Lies is a 2017 American television biopic film directed by Barry Levinson and written by Sam Levinson,
Sam Baum, and John Burnham Schwartz, based on the 2011 non-fiction book of the same name by Diana B.
The film stars Robert De Niro as businessman and fraudster Bernie Madoff, Michelle Pfeiffer as
his wife Ruth Madoff, and Alessandro Nivola as their older son Mark Madoff.
It aired on HBO on May 20, 2017.
This is the fourth film featuring De Niro and Pfeiffer, following Stardust (2007), New Year's Eve
(2011) and  The Family (2013), as well as their first collaboration for television.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, wall
street, biography, based on true story, scam.
The tone is emotional and intense.